greenriver.edu 2019-08-26

# Privacy - Green River College

## Privacy Notice

### Section A. Introduction

Thank you for visiting the Green River College Web site and reviewing our Privacy Notice. This statement addresses collection, use and security of and access to information that may be obtained through use of Green River College. This notice covers the following topics:

  * Information Collected and How it is Used
  * Personal Information and Choice
  * Public Access to Information
  * Nondisclosure of Certain Personal Information
  * Review and Correction of Personally Identifiable Information
  * Cookies and applets
  * Security
  * Disclaimer
  * Contact Information

### Section B. Information Collected and How it is Used

If you do nothing during your visit to our website but browse, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store the following information about your visit:

  1. The Internet Protocol Address and domain name used. The Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer. We use the Internet Protocol Address to direct Internet traffic to you. This address can be translated to determine the domain name of your service provider (e.g. xcompany.com or yourschool.edu);
  2. The type of browser and operating system you used;
  3. The date and time you visited this site;
  4. The Web pages or services you accessed at this site; and
  5. The website you visited prior to coming to this website.

The information we automatically collect or store is logged and used by Green River College only to improve the content of our Web services and to help us understand how people are using our services. Green River College analyzes the Web site logs to determine how our Web site is being used, so that we may continually improve the site's usefulness to the public.

#### What we collect if you volunteer information

If during your visit to our website you participate in a survey, send an email, or perform some other transaction on-line, the following additional information will be collected:

  1. The email address, and contents of email, for those who communicate with us via email.
  2. Information volunteered in response to a survey.
  3. Information volunteered through an on-line form for any other purpose.

The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats you send us.

We use your email to respond appropriately. This may be to respond to you, to address issues you may identify, to further improve our Web site, or to forward the email to another agency for appropriate action. Survey information is used to gather data on specific topics relevant to the college. Information from other on-line forms is used only for the purpose stated on the form.

### Section C. Personal Information and Choice

#### You may choose whether to provide personal information on-line.

“Personal information” is information about a natural person that is readily identifiable to that specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual's name, address, and phone number. A domain name or Internet Protocol address is not considered personal information.

We collect no personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us by sending us email, participating in a survey, or completing an online form. You may choose not to contact us by email, participate in a survey or to provide any personal information using an online form. Your choice to not participate in these activities will not impair your ability to browse the Green River College Web site and read or download any information provided on the site.

If personal information is requested on the Web site or volunteered by the user, state law and the federal Privacy Act of 1974 may protect it. However, this information is a public record once you provide it, and may be subject to public inspection and copying if not protected by federal or state law.

If you believe that your personal information is being used for a purpose other than what was intended when submitted, you may contact the Green River College Office of Public Information as shown in the Contact Information Section of this statement.

Green River College's Web site is a general audience site and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. Users are cautioned that the collection of personal information requested from or volunteered by children online or by email will be treated the same as information given by an adult, and may be subject to public access.

### Section D. Public Access to Information

In the State Of Washington, laws exist to ensure that government is open and that the public has a right to access appropriate records and information possessed by state government. At the same time, there are exceptions to the public's right to access public records that serve various needs including the privacy of individuals. Exceptions are provided by both state and federal laws.

All of the information collected at this site becomes public records that may be subject to inspection and copying by members of the public, unless an exemption in law exists. [RCW 42.56.070](http://apps.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=42.56.070 "RCW 42/56/070") states that:

Each agency, in accordance with published rules, shall make available for public inspection and copying all public records, unless the record falls within the specific exemptions of the Public Records Act or other statute which exempts or prohibits disclosure of specific information or records.

To the extent required to prevent an unreasonable invasion of personal privacy interests protected by RCW 42.56.210 and [42.56.320](http://apps.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=42.56.320 "42.56.320"), an agency shall delete identifying details in a manner consistent with [RCW 42.56.210](http://apps.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=42.56.210 "RCW 42.56.210") and RCW 42.56.320 when it makes available or publishes any public record; however, in each case, the justification for the deletion shall be explained fully in writing.

In the event of a conflict between this Privacy Notice and the Public Records Act or other law governing the agency’s disclosure of records, the Public Records Act or other applicable law will control.

### Section E. Nondisclosure of Certain Personal Information

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to pay tuition and fees online. The information is required in order to verify your identity and to verify your credit card number and its expiration date. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to apply tuition and fee payment online, and you will have to pay your tuition and fees in person.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.<.p>

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Degree Audit

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to perform a degree audit of your records over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to display a degree audit of your records over the Web, and you will have to request a degree audit in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Financial Aid Inquiry

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to obtain your financial aid status over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to give you your financial aid status over the Web, and you will have to obtain this information in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Hope and Lifetime Learning Tax Credit

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to allow you to view and copy course enrollment and payment information. The information is required in order to provide you with the tax information needed for compliance with the Internal Revenue Service reporting requirements for the Hope and Lifetime Leaning tax credits. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it, we will be unable to display your enrollment and payment information and you will have to obtain a copy of your enrollment and payment records either in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Registration

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to register for classes over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it you will be unable to register for classes over the Web, and you will have to register for classes in person

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Registration Appointments

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to obtain your registration appointment information over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to display your registration appointment information over the Web, and you will have to obtain your registration appointment information address in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Schedule Planner

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to check requisites while using schedule planner. The information is required in order to access your academic and testing records. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to verify your eligibility for enrollment into certain classes and you may be blocked from enrolling into those classes.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Student Address Change

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to change your address over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to change your address over the Web, and you will have to change your address in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Student PIN Change

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to change your personal identification number over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to change your PIN over the Web, and you will have to change your PIN in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Student Schedule

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to view your quarterly schedule. The information is required in order to verify you identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to display your quarterly schedule over the Web, and you will have to obtain a copy of your quarterly schedule in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law

#### Unofficial Transcript

Green River College may require you to provide certain personal information in order to view your unofficial transcript over the Web. The information is required in order to verify your identity. You may choose not to provide this information, but if you choose not to provide it we will be unable to display your unofficial transcript over the Web, and you will have to view your unofficial transcript in person or by mail.

The following laws and regulations may prevent Green River College from disclosing the personal information about you except for directory information. Only directory information can be released without student's authorization. Students must sign a release in order to have any other information disclosed or to withhold all information. Education information may be released to other institutions that have requested the records and in which the student seeks or intends to enroll. Information may be released to a third party without student's consent if an emergency situation exists or if information is requested officially by means of a subpoena, court order or legal report. Additionally, Congress requires student information to be released to military recruiters if officially requested. Directory information may include student's name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, major fields of study, participation in officially recognized activities and sports, weight and height of members of athletic teams, dates of attendance, degrees and awards received, the most recent previous educational agency or institution attended by the student, and other similar information.

  * [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA)](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html "FERPA") Section 438, Public Law 90-247 Title IV, as amended, 88 Stat 571-574 (20 USC 1232g) otherwise known as the Buckley Amendment Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act
  * [RCW 42.17.310](http://www.leg.wa.gov/RCW/index.cfm?section=42.17.310&fuseaction=section "RCW 42.17.310") (a) and (ss) exempts the following from public inspection and copying: (a) Personal information in any files maintained for students in public schools, patients or clients of public institutions or public health agencies, or welfare recipients; (ss) Credit card numbers, debit card numbers, electronic check numbers, card expiration dates, or bank or other financial account numbers supplied to an agency for the purpose of electronic transfer of funds, except when disclosure is expressly required by law.

### Section F. Review and Correction of Personally Identifiable Information

You can review any personally identifiable information we collect about you by using the information in the Contact Information section at the end of this Notice. You may recommend changes to your personally identifiable information you believe to be inaccurate by submitting an email or written request that credibly shows the inaccuracy. We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. ([RCW 43.105.310](http://apps.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=43.105.310 "RCW 43.105.310"))

### Section G. Cookies [and applets]

To better serve our users we are now using "cookies" to customize your browsing experience with the Green River College Web site. Cookies are simple text files stored on your computer by your Web browser.

Cookies created on your computer by using this Web site do not contain personally identifying information and do not compromise your privacy or security. We use the cookie feature to store to store the following information on your computer:

  1. Session login information
  2. Limited personal information, such as name

### Section H. Security

Green River College, as developer and manager of the Green River College Web site, has taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information maintained by Green River College. [For site security purposes and to ensure that this Web site remains available to all users, Green River College employs software to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to this Web site.] These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, and to provide reasonable protection of private information in our possession.

This information should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided via Green River College Web sites.

### Section I. Disclaimer

The Green River College Web site has many links to other Web sites. These include links to Web sites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations and private businesses. When you link to another site, you are no longer on the Green River College Web site and this Privacy Notice will not apply. When you link to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site.

Reference in this Web site to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm, or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the State of Washington, Green River College, or its officers, employees or agents.

Neither the State of Washington, nor any agency, officer, or employee of the State of Washington warrants the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published by this system, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from this system, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be incorrect or not current. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at its own risk.

Green River College reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Notice at any time without notice by posting such revised Privacy Notice at the Green River College home page.

### Section J. Green River College Contact Information

You may contact Green River College as follows:

To review your personal information, or request correction of your personal information:

Public Information Office  
Green River College  
12401 SE 320th Street  
Auburn, WA 98092  
Fax: 253-288-3460  
Phone: 253-288-3360
